anazana.com 2018-08-18

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services and websites offered by anaZana, Inc. (anaZana).

Your privacy on the Internet is very important to anaZana. anaZana strives to make your online experience satisfying and safe. If you have any question about anaZana or this Privacy you can write to us by email at [support@anaZana.com](mailto:support@anaZana.com).

 **Registration**  
In order to use our web solutions and services, a user is required to complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

 **Log information  
** When you access anaZana services via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.

 **Orders**  
We request information from you on our order forms. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name, e-mail address,contact phone) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

 **Information You Provide  
** When you sign up for an anaZana services, anaZana asks you for personal information. anaZana may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other anaZana services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of anaZana services. Your email address is used for sending you notifications concerning anaZana services.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.  
​  
When you log in to anaZana web platforms, anaZana’s servers automatically record information about the way you use anaZana. anaZana records information such as account activity and other log information including browser type, IP-address, date and time of access, cookie ID, and referrer URL.

anaZana reserves the option to collect other profile data provided by you including but not limited to profile picture, description, nickname, gender, age, education and last activities in order to interact with other anaZana users. Such information will be displayed in order to facilitate user interaction.

Please understand that when you sign into anaZana or post content, your information is not anonymous to anaZana.  
​  
 **Accessing, Updating And Control Over Personal information  
** When you use anaZana services, anaZana makes good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. anaZana asks individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and anaZana may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where anaZana provides information access and correction, anaZana performs this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Note that removed or deleted information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time.  
​  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * ​See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.​

 **Information Security  
** anaZana takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

anaZana restricts access to personal information to anaZana employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

anaZana system uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). You must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Chrom, Firefox, Safari or similar to access anaZana services. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it’s transmitted over the Internet.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

anaZana cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to anaZana and you do so at your own risk. Once anaZana receives your transmission, anaZana makes efforts to ensure security on our systems. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up-to-date antivirus software.

Please report any security violations to anaZana on support@anaZana.com.  
​  
 **Cookies**  
We use "cookies" on anaZana sites. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

When you visit anaZana, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some anaZana features or services may not function properly without cookies.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

 **Information Sharing  
** Anyone can see the public websites, online stores, portals, web-catalogs, and other web solutions you create and the profile information you give us. We also make this public information available through what are called APIs (basically a technical way to share information quickly), for example, payment processing, Google maps, etc.  
​  
We share aggregated information with our partners and advertisers. We use outside credit card processing companies to bill users for goods and services, domain registrars to provide domains, shipping companies to ship orders, and other companies to provide services.

Some of the ways we use your information require us to share information with third parties, so we can provide your anaZana experience, make sure our customization is effective and comply with laws that apply to us. We share your information with:

  * ​Other services (like Facebook or Google) when you decide to link your anaZana account to those services or publish your activity to them. For example, you can choose to publish your products or services to Facebook or Twitter.
  * Merchants you purchase from on anaZana websites and portals. When you buy something on anaZana websites using your payment card, we share information necessary for you to make your purchase, such as your payment card information, contact information, and other information about the transaction with the merchant you’re buying from. For more information on what we share with merchants, see our Support Center.
  * Online advertisers (like Facebook or Google) and third party companies that we or they use to audit or improve the delivery and performance of ads or content on websites, portals and online stores (for example, through Google Analytics or Facebook Pixel). To learn more about third party companies that analyze ad performance, please contact our Support Center.
  * Third party companies or individuals that we employ to process information on our behalf based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy. For example, we share payment card information with the payment companies we use to store your payment information. We also share data with security consultants to help us get better at identifying spam. Some information we acquire may be collected by third party providers on our behalf.
  * Law enforcement agencies or government agencies. We only share information if we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety, rights, or property of the public, any person, or anaZana; or to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * Our wholly owned subsidiaries and affiliates. If we were to engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this Policy, we would share your information with a party involved in such a process (for example, a potential purchaser).

If anaZana buys or sells all or a part of business, personally identifiable information you have shared with anaZana is generally one of the business assets that will be transferred. The transferred personally identifiable information will remain subject to the promises made in this Policy or subsequent policies to which you have consented.

Our websites contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our sites and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

 **Content  
** Any Content uploaded or created using anaZana service is by default hosted for the public and are thus publicly accessible unless explicitly protected by the website's owner optional protection setting.

Please note that even if you do not publish links to Content or submit links to a search engine, individuals or search engines may discover and link to your Content by data-mining, guessing the address, spidering sites, or other methods. If you are concerned about the privacy or confidentiality of Content that you produce, please take all appropriate steps to ensure that sensitive materials are password-protected. anazana makes no guarantee as to the reliability or security of the protection setting feature.  
​  
 **User Communications  
** When you send email or other communications to anaZana, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

 **Age Requirements For Use Of anaZana  
** anaZana is available for individuals aged 18 years or older.

If you are based in the EEA you may only use anaZana if you are over the age at which you can provide consent to data processing under the laws of your country or if verifiable parental consent for your use of anaZana has been provided to us. If you are a parent and you learn that your child is using anaZana and you don't want them to, please contact us.  
​  
 **Your Options  
** You have options in relation to the information that we have about you described below. To exercise these options, please contact us. If you're an EEA user, you can:

  * Access the information we hold about you. We'll usually share this with you within 30 days of you asking us for it.
  * Have your information corrected or deleted. You can update your information in your settings. If you have problems updating the information or if you would like us to delete it, contact us.
  * Object to us processing your information. You can ask us to stop using your information, including when we use your information to send you marketing emails or push notifications. If you opt out of receiving marketing messages from us, we may still send you newsletters and updates about your account. We only send you marketing material if you've agreed to it, but if you'd rather we don't, you can easily unsubscribe at any time.
  * Have the information you provided to us sent to another organization, where we hold this information with your consent or for the performance of a contract with you, where it's technically feasible.
  * Complain to a regulator. If you're based in the EEA and think that we haven't complied with data protection laws, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the Data Protection Commission in Ireland or with your local supervisory authority.

 **How We Make Changes To This Policy  
** Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your anaZana account or notify you by publication here.

The best way to get in touch is through the Support Center:  
[support@anazana.com  
](mailto:support@anazana.com)Data Protection Officer  
anaZana, Inc.  
600 West Broadway, Ste 700  
San Diego, CA 92101, USA

Effective April 18Th, 2018
